Hello everyone.  In today's video we are going to talk
about ICICI Prudential Company.  So this company is going to be listed today
on the BSE and NSE exchanges through IPO.
But
before that, some breaking updates are coming.
Like GMP saw record breaking
rise.  But
how much premium or
profit can be made on one lot size?  Today, on the
day of listing, we will check them
and also try to know what is the big update on the listing.
But for those who have been allotted in this IPO, we will
also discuss what should be the strategy for them.  So
you must stay till the end of the video.  Today's
video is going to be very important for all the allottees.
So
friends, perhaps your
shares might have become available here now.  If you have got one lot
size, then six
equity shares at the price of ₹2165 will be credited to your demat account.
As you
can see here friends.  Well, yesterday was the
time to credit it.  But
friends, if you see today, its listing is going to happen on 19th December.
But even before that,
friends, the biggest surprise you will see is
that its GMP will be seen rocketing to around ₹520.
Meaning that friends, if
you see this late last night, then there has been an increase of around ₹150, that is,
around ₹150.
Thanks to the day before yesterday, that means friends, GMP increased from ₹370 to
₹520.  Meaning that
friends, here the premium will increase by around 7%.
As you can see it
was 24% here late last night but
before that it was around 17% which you can still see is
showing a premium of 24% here.
So friends, here the final price of ₹2165 has been
arrived at, so if you
apply GMP of ₹520 on it, then the
estimated listing update of ₹2685 is seen,
which shows a premium of around 24%.
But friends, if we talk about one lot size, then
you can see that the
estimated updates are going on around ₹3120.
Which friends is according to this GMP.
But friends, I would like to tell you that these
GMPs are estimated figures
and companies never list according to them.
So friends, it is
also possible that this may be seen happening around double
here.  It is also possible
that half of this may remain, friends.  So
anything can happen here.  Well,
friends, if we believe the updates going on here
regarding this IPO or this company, then
friends, approximately this much should happen here.
But some experts have
given updates of around 39, that is, 39% from this price.  So if this
happens here then friends, almost a
very good position can be achieved here
today on the day of listing.  However,
friends, how will the company list, as
you must be aware here, there is a rule of T Plus One
and according to that the company
lists as per this rule of SEBI.
Now friends,
you will get time from 9:30 am to around 4:45 pm in
which you will be able to put the bud and
also hold it here.  Now
friends, those who have got the allotment,
they
can sell it here, they can buy it, they can do
anything.  But those who have
not been allotted, they
can only create an environment of shopping or buying here.
So now friends, here those who have been allotted
and those who have not been allotted,
a pre-opening session will be held within these 15 minutes between 9:30 and around 9:45.
Within that, the price at which there will be
maximum buying and selling will be
locked and the company will be
listed at that price.  Meaning that friends,
if I tell you as an example,
according to this GMP, there is a price of ₹2685.
You can take an example and
on this example, friends, most of the people who have got
allotment here and those who have
not got allotment, they mostly
publish the sale buy update at this price here and
put up bids etc.  So friends, this price will be
locked and on this basis the
company will be listed here on BSE NC.
So friends, this is how the
listing of any company happens here on the exchanges of BSE and NSE, as per T Plus One.
But friends, now the
biggest thing comes that in this you
must avoid the work of big operators.  Now, as
you know friends, in this company
or in this IPO, you
can see that funds have been invested in very large quantities,
around Rs 7600 crore, Rs 25000 crore, Rs
33000 crore.  So these friends
fill lot size of 1000, 2000, 10000 in one go.
Due to which, friends, they get at least a thousand lot size.
So friends, now, for
example, here, 10,000, sorry, here, around
1000 lot sizes are available
to someone, for example, take the small NA category, if
you get it, then
friends, it will be updated around 31200,
according to this GMP. But
friends, if he books this here, then
you can understand that there can be a
lot of negative pressure on the price here,
because friends, booking such a large
quantity here in one go, then
you can understand
how much pressure can be created here, so
because of that, friends, when it comes down here, it is
very high, so it is possible
that friends, friends, they may hold again,
because friends, here
they have already booked such a large fund,
but after that, friends, they
can book the shares here even at cheap prices,
due to which this happens, friends, friends, friends, the double game
listing strategy, which is of the operators,
so because of this, friends, here you
can also avoid the operator game, those who have a
long-term view, so
friends,  I have not seen that here but if
they are short term and medium term, then
friends, they should definitely consult their financial advisor here.  You
must also take the long term ones because friends, this is
only a video which is being provided for innovative purposes
only.  However
friends, now let us know the news here
day by day listing.  So first of all
friends, I would like to show you here.
As you can see, considering the
strong presence of ICICI Bank and Productional, its
extensive growth in the digital sector and low risk across all the schemes,
some experts are saying that
Productional can
achieve better valuations than its peers.
Now, friends, here
is SBI Mutual Fund, it has a
share of about 14% in the entire market.
But friends, this ICICI
mutual fund gives approximately 13.3%.  So
friends, when this company ICICI gets listed here, then
you can understand that
it can also hit SBI here, which can be a
very good positive point here.
And its strong position in the market,
domestic savings finance, whatever is
long term here, looking at the long term
updates, friends Prashant Tapse is the
senior research vice president of Mehta Equities,
friends, you
can see here that he has given a
very good update for the long term purpose company.
However, friends, he further
said that we
can see the investors at the time of listing.  Updates from Long Term Purpose
advise here.  This is all
they have to say and investors who have
not been allotted shares can
also check for them.  They say that
we can see the shares here on the day of listing.  We
provide these updates here.
But he has not advised any haste here.
So
friends, do not be in a hurry at all because
after the listing,
you can suggest entering here at the appropriate time
because friends, it is
possible that something very strong momentum may be
seen here.  So for this reason,
you should not be in a hurry here at all because
friends, amidst the cautious market sentiment, the
instability in the near future and the valuation situation
and the possibilities here
cannot be denied here because
friends, something can go wrong here
if you take some action here on the day of listing, then you
can see like this,
friends, a
big statement came from a big expert here, but friends, you
can see here that an expert has
given updates of around 39%, although you
can see his update here, the update had already
come which I had told you by discussing it in yesterday's video, so
friends, here is the
senior vice president of PL Capital.
Those who can see that they have
provided this rating here,
but you can also see that this update should
also be released here, which you
can see by pausing the video and you
can also see the 39%,
they have shown the update here.  So friends, here
I am not registered with SEBI, hence I am
not telling anything here after reading it.  But friends, whatever
updates are there, this is
not my advice here or only
friends, this is being told to you by a knowledgeable person here.
But friends,
you can now see whatever updates are there here.
Here, by pausing the video on the screen,
these updates are being given here
by many experts only.
But friends, now the business of this company here
is much better and
because of this, friends, you can see that the company has
established its huge dominance here in the entire
market.  As you
can see, here the company manages active mutual fund assets worth around Rs 10.1 lakh crore
and friends, you
can also see that this company holds a market share of around 13.3%
in the whole of India
and friends, you will be seeing a very big update even
before its delisting.
Although friends, the company has many
branches.  As you can see here, the number
of this product is around 272, but if
you look at the bank itself, it is more than 7000.  So
friends, the company will definitely make profit here
because of this update.
But friends, here are
some big updates regarding this IPO which have been discussed with you.
But now friends,
whatever updates will happen even after the listing, they will be
updated to you in the late evening video.
So you must subscribe to our channel.